Hey, trap stars. Look at my sleeves. Just checking in to see if you're ready to admit that these
longtime Democrat loving black folks, right? These longtime centrist Negroes who be on your TV
screens on mainstream media, et cetera, YouTube. I'm just wondering if you're ready to admit that
the fact that they keep Trump as their main beacon of everything that's wrong all the time
yeah, that's, that's about content, not movement. The fact that they never actually questioned the
Democrats or why their money is always going everywhere, but the communities that they claim
to speak for. Yeah, that's about access, not progress. So I'm just wondering if today we're
willing to, to make that, um, I'm just wondering if today we're ready to say what that is so that
we can start actually paying attention and listening to folks who have a much deeper and more advanced
perspective and are actually visionaries instead of political payrollees. My ultimate goal is the
liberation of liberation of my people. We are of this land.
My little shop.